Its name is Quetzalcoatl. Just call it Q. That's all you'll
have time to say before it tears you apart!
Q is a crime, horror, mystery film directed by Larry Cohen.
A fleeing gangland flunky discovers the New York nest of Aztec
deity Quetzalcoatl, the man-eating flying serpent.
Jimmy Quinn, played by Michael Moriarty.
Joan, played by Candy Clark.
Shepard, played by David Carradine.
Powell, played by Richard Roundtree.
Lt. Murray, played by James Dixon.
Commissioner, played by Malachy McCourt.
Q – The Winged Serpent (also known as Q) is a 1982 American monster horror film written, co-produced and directed
by Larry Cohen and starring Michael Moriarty, Candy Clark, David Carradine and Richard Roundtree.
The film follows a petty swindler (Moriarty) who accidentally intrudes in a case
involving a winged deity monster that poses a threat to New York City.
He is the only person who has information that can
help the police to stop the creature.
The film explores themes of new york city, monster,
legend, mexica (aztec), ritual murder.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.